# Jed Hsu

4321 Margery Dr., Fremont, CA 94538 :: (510) 789-5146 :: jedhsu11@gmail.com

## SUMMARY

MS Engineering & MBA graduate pursuing a Software Engineer position. Extensive experience in managing projects and teams, programming lasers and metrology tools, developing products, defining specifications, performing QA and reliability tests, and interfacing with international contract manufacturers.

### **SOFTWARE PROJECTS**

Website: challenge50.herokuapp.com

Github: github.com/jedh1/challenge50

- Marriott Search A web scraper that sends daily email results for users to track Marriott hotel prices
  - o A separate thread sends the user's form input to Marriott.com.
  - o Selenium framework scrapes search results, and the data is emailed.
  - o APScheduler Python package with Django schedules recurring jobs.
  - o A Postgres database stores search results, and they can be retrieved and deleted.
- Stock Back Testing App that calculates and plots stock trades using the moving average crossover strategy
  - o The user can input a stock ticker and strategy parameters.
  - O Yfinance Python package obtains data from Yahoo Finance, and the Pandas package reads the data.
  - o The Backtrader package calculates the results, and Plotly graphs the output.
- "30days30projects" A challenge to complete 30 projects in 30 days (5/13/20 6/11/20). Highlights:
  - o Floppy Bird Game: A simple version of the popular Flappy Bird mobile game using mainly JavaScript.
  - o Meal Finder: A JavaScript and CSS project that finds recipes based on user's input.
  - o Breakout Game: One round of the classic Breakout game using JavaScript and HTML5 Canvas.
  - o Flash Cards: A CSS project that creates flash cards animations, and local storage keeps the cards.
  - o XY Plotter: A Python project that uses the Pandas and Plotly packages. The user can import a csv file, and the app outputs an XY plot with the Z values color-coded.

## **EXPERIENCE**

Translarity, Inc.

Development Engineering Manager

Fremont, CA

December 2015 – Present

Banyan Energy, Inc. R&D Project Manager

Fremont, CA

October 2011 – December 2015

SunPower Corporation R&D Reliability Engineer

Richmond, CA

June 2010 – October 2011

#### SKILLS, INTERESTS, AWARDS

- Languages and Frameworks: Python, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Django, Flask
- Six Sigma Green Belt certified
- Passionate about teaching Private tutor from January 2009 through February 2020
- "Best Data Presentation" awarded at SWTest Asia 2019 the largest conference in the probe card industry

## **EDUCATION**

San Jose State University University of California, Berkeley MBA, 2016 and M.S. Engineering (Systems Engineering), 2016

B.S. Chemical Engineering, 2011